Thank you for watching!
Thanks for your work!
Hallo! Ste, this time with Yuhane Yamazaki of Ami Morikawa of Beyooooonds's Candy and
Hirai Miyo from Beyooooonds's Seasonings.
Please stay with us until the end of the show.
This weekend, March 30th and 31st, Hello Project Hina Fest 2024 will be held!
It's finally here!
This is an event that comes around once a year.
Yes!
What are you looking forward to at this year's Hina Fest?
We'll be a shuffle unit this time.
Congratulations.
We won the lottery.
That's great.
We'll be performing as a trio at the noon show on the 31st.
Congratulations!
Thank you very much.
Shiori Nishida, Kirara Nemura and I will do our best.
Please look forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it!
I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm sure you must be very nervous.
I'm sure you must be really nervous.
I'm really rooting for you, so please do your best.
I'll do my best.
And BEYOND will start concerts and live performances next week!
Yes!
BEYOND PHONIC 2 will be held on April 6 at Tokyo Metropolitan Art Space
and on May 10 at Kobe International Conference Hall.
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much.
I will do my best again!
And from April 7, BEYOND LIVE TOUR 2024 SPRING
Personality will start from Hiroshima!
Yes, sir.
First of all, I would like to talk about BEYOND PHONIC 2.
The first part is arranged as an orchestra.
I think it's going to be a really magnificent space.
I can say now that the previous BEYOND PHONIC PART 1
It was really a single performance.
So the tickets were sold out right away.
I think there were a lot of people who couldn't see the show.
This time, there will be 3 shows in 2 cities.
I'm very happy about that.
I think more people will be able to see the show.
Yes, sir.
And as for the spring tour...
This will be BEYOND's first live house tour.
I'm so happy.
Finally.
Yes, just like the title says.
I hope we can give you a concert where each of you can shine with your own individuality.
And since it's in a live house, we'll be very close to you all.
So I hope we can look you in the eye a lot.
I hope the concert will be a concert with a sense of unity.
I will do my best!
Please take a look at this video.
Please watch it.
Thank you very much for watching.
Are you sitting down, staff?
On your feet, then.
It would be a little more interesting if you could sit down.
Oh, that?
It's a hammer in the back. It's a hammer in the back.
That's quite a robbery, isn't it?
I'm nervous,
But we rehearsed a lot,
I'm nervous, but I'm sure it will be over before I know it,
I feel like I'll be fine. I'm feeling okay now.
But I still have a lot of things to think about,
I'm going to catch up with the store.
By myself. I'll do my best.
But I think I'm getting the best out of this place,
I really, really want everyone to be able to do their own thing,
I want everyone to be free to do their own thing,
I'd rather see the normal members than the ones who are tied down,
I want you to see the members in their everyday lives, rather than the members who are tied down,
I want them to be free and uninhibited,
I want them to be free and uninhibited, and I will do my best to take responsibility for my part in the project.
Congratulations!
Yay!
Wow, it's gorgeous!
It's so cute!
Thank you so much!
Looks delicious!
I've received so much love from everyone since this morning, I've been so happy and full of energy.
Yes!
Let's do our best every day!
I know you must be nervous, but I'm sure you'll be nervous about singing, but you'll be fine,
Don't worry! We can all do it!
We have done it until now.
Well, I'll do my best with my heart, Elim!
Yes, I'll do my best!
Let's do our best!
Please do!
ED
More than the snow at night
More than diamonds in the dunkaratto
I just want you to be by my side
I understand
Hey baby
Don't tell me you want to cry
I don't take either one of you for granted
I don't trust myself
I'm right here
Love.
More
Information
More.
No matter what.
Unforgivable
More.
I want you to do it all the time.
Ah, on this planet.
How many lovers are there on this planet?
Come on, hold my hand, let's go out into the universe
1. a little nervous
2. put on your Harris suit
3. try a little harder
I'm waiting for you
4. i just wanted you to shut up
5. touch me
6. i want you to smile
I'm waiting for you
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I'm by your side right now, every moment of every day I love you
How many kisses are better than I love you
How many kisses are better than I love you?
Isn't it strange being a girl?
You know what I mean?
Hey baby
I can't wait to call you.
I'm sick to my stomach.
How many times do I have to call you?
You're making my stomach churn.
Zimbascha...
It's just a little...
Awkward
A girl's a girl
I'm always on the edge of my seat
Ah, in this dream
How many possibilities
How much potential does this dream have?
Come on, admit it all
I believe in the future
Three, you're so cute, even when you're all puffed up
1. My feelings.
2 I'm trying to fulfill them.
3 You're the most beautiful girl I've ever seen
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you.
I love you.
Get it!
Juice to be told
To be funny to be told
Sweet Just a little more
Wow. Wow. Wow.
Juice to be told
Sweet, just hang in there a little longer
Hold on to each day
I want you to change I want you to change
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I'll always be by your side
I love you
Meow Man
Wiem يام
Wiem
Yea.
Enjoying it? Watch the rest of the show!
This is Hirai Miyo from Beyond Seasonings, Halo! I'm going to start talking a little bit about each other.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
The second photo book "Belief" will be released on April 10.
What kind of photos do you feel you have grown since your first photo book? The ones where my abs and back muscles are leaking.
What is your favorite musical play and character that you would like to see performed?
And Jackie from Me & My Girl. What do you like to do these days? Watching video games.
What is your secret to not becoming a 3-day monk?
Take the long view!
This summer marks the 5th anniversary of Beyooooonds's major label debut.
The moment I heard the announcement at the release event of our major label debut that we were No.1 on Oricon!
I was so excited! Thank you very much.
There were a few things that caught my attention. First of all, congratulations on your second photo book!
Your abs and back muscles are amazing!
I've been going to the gym, and I've been thinking about how to reduce body fat and build muscle mass, and I've been working on my diet.
There were a lot of shots where the light was really good and there were shadows, and I think that's where I've grown since the last time, so please pay attention.
And this is connected to what I was saying earlier about Mio-chan, she is very stoic.
I asked you a while ago how to avoid becoming a 3-day monk. Well, I think it's easy to set a goal of three days, but I don't think it's a hurdle to overcome.
But it's not just a matter of continuing for three days. If you take a day off, you can start again the next day, and have the courage to switch on and off.
Continuation is the most important thing, so it's okay to take a break.
It's important to be able to resume afterwards. I'm a little motivated now.
I tend to be a three-day monk, but you're right, it's okay to take a break.
I see. Thank you, Ms. Hirai. I'll do my best.
We'll leave the questions for Yuhane-chan for after the VTR.
Hello! Sta!
Kecchu!
Is it because of the summer?
Wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan wacchan tea no mama!
Tea Horse, first album, Channel 1, now on sale!
Hallo! Ste!
Next, I would like to ask a question to Yuhane-chan from me. Yes, please. Yes, please. I'd like to ask you what you want to do for the new grade. Tell us what you want to do for your new grade.
Yes, I want to be able to make comfortable greetings. I will perform at the Hello Project trainees' presentation at the beginning of this month.
How did you feel after performing at the trainees' presentation after a long time? I feel old.
What is the latest hair arrangement that has been a hit for you? The inner curls.
You are very expressive, Yuhane. What do you keep in mind when you perform? I try to put a nice smile on my face while looking at the faces of the cheering audience.
What is Doraemon's secret tool that is perfect for Beyooooonds? Yes, the Archecopter!
Thank you very much.
Oh. I was just thinking about the trainee presentation and how I'm getting old.
Yes, the trainee recital really had a unique sense of tension, and I was dancing with all my might,
The trainee songs were very strenuous. There were many parts where everyone had to sing together, so we had to dance while singing all the time,
It was a really hard situation. I don't know if I'm tired, I'm not tired,
I don't feel tired, but there were moments when I felt like I was getting a little old. I was not a trainee at the presentation, but I really looked up to everyone.
I think they are really great. Next, the secret tool of Doraemon that is perfect for Beyoncé is the Archecopter.
Why? Because the Beyoncés want to fly with a "beyonnnn". So let's all put on Takekopters and fly wherever we want!
That's great! Thank you very much!
Hallo! We will continue after this!
This is Natsuyaki Masashi.
This is NIKYO SHIMOITA from ANGELUM.
I will continue to cook hard!
Yes, let's do our best!
So, what are we going to cook this time?
I'm going to make a meat bun and a red bean paste bun.
That's nice.
My first time! I'm really looking forward to it.
I'm really looking forward to it. Do you cook, Yukiho?
A little?
Yes, I do.
Then let's have fun today,
Fun is the best.
Let's have fun!
Wow, plump.
That's good, that's good.
Let's go out with a bang.
It's fun.
Yes, it's OK to mix it up.
So, where do we start this time?
Yes, now it's time to take out the dough,
Yes.
I'd like to make them one by one.
Yes!
Let's go for it!
Wow!
That's good, isn't it?
Wow, nice!
It's nice.
Round and round!
It's glossy, isn't it?
Amazing!
It looks like a big steamed bun.
Already.
And here's how to take it out,
I'm going to take this one out while keeping the inner side around,
It's pretty much stuck to the bottom of the bun,
So, you have to turn the powder to the bottom.
Can you do that?
Where is it?
Here it is!
Here you go, Yuki.
But I'll do my best!
Okay, great.
Wow, wow, wow.
It already looks delicious.
A little bit. I want to keep this glossy look, don't you?
Try it with the teacher.
Like this.
OK.
Looks good.
What's fun to do when you're 17?
It's fun to hang out in the dressing room.
I see. You must love the members.
What are they doing? Everyone is in the dressing room.
Basically, we do makeup,
Sometimes we play cards.
Mr. Hashimoto brought a card game,
We say who wants to play and raise our hands to play,
You have to raise your hand.
Raise your hand,
And then we all play together.
Not only those who want to do it, but everyone does it.
I see.
It should be interesting since there are a lot of people.
That's nice. We're all friends.
And now it's time to start making the an-man, the seed of my example,
Here's Miyamizu's point!
Don't make the center too thin!
If you make them the same thickness,
If you wrap them the same thickness, the bottom part will stretch and become thinner,
If the bottom part gets stretched and becomes thin, it will come out when you wrap it with cooking paper.
If you do it the same thickness, after wrapping, the bottom part will stretch and become thinner. If it is too thin, the contents will come out.
So, leave the base as thick as possible.
Put it on your left hand.
It looks like you are making mini pizzas.
Yes, that's right. I guess you could do that too.
Just do the first step like this,
And don't move your thumb here,
I heard that you just pinch it without moving your thumb,
It's difficult.
But it's hard to do,
Like this?
Yes.
What's this?
Is this the teacher's?
No, this one.
It's a little bit stale.
You're a little fast with this one, aren't you?
It's too smooth. It's a little difficult.
Is it done?
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
It's good. It's good.
And if you just give it a little more tug...
I'm probably prettier than you.
Really? - Yeah.
Oh, it's wrapped so well.
It's like your teeth.
But there was a lot of angst.
I feel like I've seen something like this before.
It's like he's a bad teacher.
The teacher's teacher is so cute.
Different songs every time at Angerme.
You know, a lot of songs in different genres.
Yes, they do.
What do you like best?
At live shows and stuff.
I like the fun ones.
So the new songs are pretty good?
Oh, yeah.
The one that's more fun to play live
Life is Beautiful is more fun to play live.
But the one I feel like I've done is Redline.
The one with a lot of guts.
They're both good, aren't they?
They're both good.
They're so good!
It's a cute look, isn't it?
Thank you.
You're good.
Very good.
We'll rest for about 20 minutes.
Just enough time for a nap.
Okay, now that the second nap is over, let's open the door to see how it's done.
It feels so good!
This one is more luminous than the other one, I guess because we made this one first.
Only two people can enter each of these, so please choose.
Okay, these two.
The bottom one should be a bun, and the top one should be a bean-jam bun.
Let's start with the bun.
This one.
Hot.
About 15 minutes.
We'll wait.
During this time.
I'm sure you have questions.
Ask your seniors.
Something that might embarrass you.
Troubling?
This is something that probably bothers all of you.
What is your beauty secret?
The secret of beauty
The secret of beauty is already proven.
But it's still very dry.
I pack my face every day.
I definitely pack every night and morning.
That's because I started in elementary school.
It's not common to wear makeup in elementary school.
But because I was working, I wore makeup all the time.
Like foundation.
That's why I'm more concerned about wrinkles
wrinkles and other things that you worry about when you grow up.
So I was always told to do it early.
I was always told that.
I skipped it when I was a teenager.
That's exactly what I was thinking.
I thought my teenage skin was invincible.
I didn't even apply lotion or milky lotion.
Is that right?
I thought my skin had changed a little since I entered my 20s.
I thought my skin had changed a little.
But I still thought I was invincible.
But then I started to feel like I was invincible.
I'm starting to realize that I haven't kept up with what the adults have been telling me.
I didn't follow what the adults told me to do.
Dryness...
or spots, or acne-prone.
I should have done it every day.
I should have done the pack every day.
This is a great harvest, isn't it?
I'm glad I listened to you.
Now it's been 15 minutes.
I'm a little nervous.
I'm a little wobbly, so I'm going to let you go.
Open.
Oh, my gosh!
It's so plump!
Put it down.
That's great.
It's so good!
The bottom is a steamed bun.
That's great.
Wow, wow, wow, wow.
Looks so delicious!
Finished!
The steamed buns and bean-jam buns are ready.
It's done!
Yukio, what do you think?
Look at this. Look how it turned out.
Is the show on?
No, it's started.
Please take a look. This way.
Fluffy buns and bean jam buns.
They turned out well.
Wanmaru.
Please try it right away.
I'd like to eat it first.
Then I'll break it open.
How is it?
Looks delicious.
Wow, wow, wow. It's done well.
Then I'd like to eat it.
Bon appétit.
Here you go.
Mmmm.
It's delicious. I've had it.
What's this feeling of fullness from all this stuffing? It's a euphoric feeling.
Then try the steamed buns. Yes, I'll have some.
Looks so good.
Second bite, it definitely is.
The juices from the meat inside the filling juices just pop in your mouth,
The taste, the oil from the sesame oil, and the green onions are quite strong,
I also felt the oil from the sesame oil and the green onion,
It's a great mix,
It's all in harmony, is it a good match?
Yes, it is. It is very tasty.
I'm glad.
I hope you will cook again on this day.
Yes, I will.
Please come visit Hello!
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
That's all for Hello!
This is Hello! Project. Project Chokotto No. 1!
Project, we conducted a survey on a slightly different theme to all the members of Hello! We will announce who is No. 1 in a ranking format.
By the way, Hirai Miyo. She came in second in the ranking of the members who are stoic anyway!
Everyone thinks so. That's what I'm talking about. I am so happy. I didn't think I would be chosen in the overall survey, so I am honored.
I will continue to work hard as a stoic. Congratulations. Thank you very much.
Now, for this year's theme, we would like the members to coordinate their fashion.
There are a lot of fashionable people here. There certainly are a lot of them.
I wonder who it is. But I'm sure it's her. I have a bit of an imagination.
Let's take a look at the ranking. First of all, third place.
The comment from the voting members is that her personal clothes show her individuality without sacrificing elegance, that she is my type, that her combinations are innovative, and that she seems to be able to create wonderful coordinates that I could never come up with.
Rin Kawana answers.
On the other hand, I thought it was great that she could wear any kind of clothes stylishly.
Haruka Inoue says.
I wonder who it is. I am looking forward to it.
The member whom I would like to see coordinate fashion. Third place went to Morning Musume。's Rio Sakurai, who received 12 votes. 24's Rio Sakurai.
I love her too. For sure. I really like Rio's fashion.
I think she has a very mode-oriented look, and I think she uses items very well. It's wonderful, isn't it?
It's certainly a convincing dunk-in.
Congratulations! It was Rio-chan.
Hallo! Ste.
Next in second place were the comments from the voting members: I have always loved fashion and think it is fashionable, so I would like to have them coordinate.
Saya Eguchi said, "I think she has always been cute and fashionable, so I would like her to coordinate her fashion. I have always wanted to wear the kind of clothes she often wears, but I don't know how to get my hands on them, so I would love to hear what she has to say.
Reina Yokoyama says. Who's that? Who is it? The second place for the member who wants to coordinate fashion is
Ayano Kawamura of Angerme, who received 15 votes.
She's cute, isn't she? She's cute. She's amazing.
I see. Where can I get that item? I mean, where can I get that item?
It really suits you, doesn't it? It's cute, isn't it? I can't describe it in words, but it's just lovely.
You have a great sense of style. I always think it's a cute line of clothing that looks like it could be in a picture book.
Congratulations. The first place winner will be announced after the VTR.
Thank you for watching!
It's a colorful day.
Predictions are predictions, inside is inside. I know, I know.
I'm sorry I couldn't say it better myself.
Oh baby
It's a day when I've had the best day of my life
that's me in the mirror
Everyone complimented me on how different I was from everyone else
Oh baby, that's me
Oh baby
I'm so bad at this.
Is that the answer again?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Sweat and tears
Ah.
Angels are shining.
And one by one, they make the earth glow.
Color, color, color, fly
I can't be someone else's rainbow
The colors are endless
Everything that pours down
Pray for strength
I wonder where I'm going
It's so hard to say
I mean, if it's like that, if it's where I'm going
It's so easy to say where you're going.
Yes, that's it! That's it!
I can't decide for myself.
Someone has to stop.
There's got to be more people out there who'll notice.
I'm just going through the motions.
Our days are not the same
Every street is infinite
Let every mixed feeling turn into a color
It's hirotori no hi
You'll never know unless you try
The future doesn't point that way
You'll never end up the way you want
The path you've chosen
It's hirotori no hi yo
To be someone else's rainbow
The hirotori is endless
Everything that comes down
Be a force to be reckoned with
Yay!
Let's work together!
Beyooooonds Rain Forest Kawai's Yuka Yamazaki and Beyooooonds Seasonings' Miyo Hirai present Halo! Hello Project Chotto Number One!
Hello Project Chotto Number One: What member would you like to have as a fashion coordinator?
The third place goes to Rio Sakurai with 12 votes and the second place goes to Ayano Kawamura with 15 votes.
As a matter of fact, there was a member who wanted the MC to coordinate today's fashion.
Wakana Matsumoto from Angerme said, "I always think your clothes are very fashionable.
I'm so glad to hear that, but you know what, Wakana, you always like my fashion.
I'm so happy that she's always telling me how much she likes my fashion, and that I'm always talking to her.
I wondered if she was getting in trouble, but if that's what you think, I'm very happy to hear it and I'm always ready to coordinate with you.
Now, the No. 1 member who wants you to coordinate your fashion is this person!
The clothes she wears in her daily life and the clothes she uploads on Instagram are very fashionable.
Her existence itself is also very fashionable.
She is cute, cool, and very nice.
She is stylish and cool from head to toe
and because she can also dress cute.
I personally wanted her to coordinate a look that would suit me.
I'm always ready to go to the airport or on the train.
I always look stylish from my toes to the top of my head.
I've seen her in many magazines, so I think she's very good at what she does.
The No. 1 member I'd like to see coordinate her fashion is
Rikako Sasaki of Angerme!
This is Rikako Sasaki from Angerme!
She chose me as the No. 1 member whom she would like to have a fashion coordinator!
I'm so embarrassed! Thank you very much!
I'm so happy to hear that I've been chosen as the number one by all the cute and adorable Halomen.
I really love clothes.
I'm the same way with my Instagram and my work.
I've been doing my own personal clothing projects and posting about them.
I feel happy and a little embarrassed at the same time, knowing that people are watching me.
I feel happy and a little embarrassed at the same time.
Sometimes I get teased about my stylishness, but this time
But this time, I'm really happy.
Thank you very much, everyone!
I really like to change colors depending on my mood.
That's why I choose my clothes first thing in the morning.
When I decide on an outfit the day before, I don't really start the day early, unless I have a very early start the next morning or something like that.
Unless I'm very early the next morning or something like that, I really choose my clothes at the beginning of the day.
I express my feeling that I want to wear this color today.
Colors and clothes.
I also make sure to put patterns in my clothes.
What I've been struggling with lately is the balance between the hem of my trousers and my shoes.
This is something I haven't been able to get right recently.
I'm thinking that I need to study more about fashion.
I'd like to introduce one of my recommended outfits here.
I think you can see the picture now.
I took this picture in December last year, right?
I think it was red in January.
This is a very heavy knit cardigan, and I'm wearing it over the cardigan.
That's the main coordination.
The overall color and material is based on denim, but as you can see, there are orange, yellow, and yellowish colors.
As you can see, there are three colors of orange, yellow, and blue.
As you can see, he is wearing three colors, orange, yellow and blue.
His hair is orange, his tie is yellow, and everything else is blue.
It's a pretty uniform coordination.
I put a striped shirt inside.
I put a striped shirt inside, a denim jacket on top of that, and a knit over that.
I like layering clothes.
Also, the tie is a key point.
I think this is a well-coordinated and well-balanced look.
Including the hair.
He wears his glasses up.
The thickness of the hair and the way the hair is pulled up make it look very well balanced.
I don't think you can see the bottom part in the photo.
It's denim and denim.
The bottom is also denim.
The shoes are Paraboots, my favorite loafers.
I have a pair of loafers called Paraboots.
I'm wearing them.
Also, you can't see it in the picture.
but what I like the most is the vintage outerwear.
I really like to make one-of-a-kind pieces.
So maybe...
If you've been following us for a while, you might know what I'm talking about.
I'd be very happy if you could take a look at my instagram and so on.
Is that good?
I'm sure everyone will agree.
They're really stylish.
The shoes are also in various genres.
Sometimes he wears really cool classic leather shoes.
Sometimes he wears cool sneakers.
And when we went out together, he was wearing a hat with an amazing pelvis.
It was just too nice.
I had to take a picture of it.
I learned a lot about how to use items.
And the colors... I didn't know you could combine those colors with each other.
It's totally cohesive and wonderful.
It's a dream come true to have them all coordinated.
I'd love to have you do it.
Hello! Hello!
This is Yuhane Yamazaki from Beyooooonds Ame no Mori Kawahama and Miyo Hirai from Beyooooonds Seasonings.
Beyooooonds Seasonings' Michiyo Hirai presents "Halo! Sta.
It's time to say goodbye!
Here is an announcement!
Hina Fest 2024 will be held on March 30th and 31st at Makuhari Messe.
We are looking forward to seeing you all there!
We are also looking forward to seeing you all at the "Carbon Neutral 2024 by Satomi Satoyama Movement" on March 30 and 31 at Makuhari Messe.
We will be releasing Miyo Hirai's second photo book, BELIEF, on April 10. We have been working hard for the past 5 months to get it ready, so we hope you will be able to pick it up!
Hello Project 25th Anniversary Concert Theme of Hello all for one and one for all is now available on Blu-ray!
It's really a concert to commemorate the 25th anniversary, so please watch it!
Biophonic2 will be held on April 6th at the Tokyo Metropolitan Art Space and on May 10th at the Kobe International Conference Center.
We hope to spend a wonderful time with you all!
Beyooooonds's first live house tour, and we are looking forward to seeing you there.
This Blu-ray includes the Tokyo and Osaka shows, so please check it out!
Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyooooonds May 8th Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8 Beyooooonds on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8, Beyo nce on May 8
I'm so excited that I will be performing on such a big stage that I never dreamed of.
We will do our best to prepare for this event, and we hope you will come to see us.
I hope you will come to the show. Project will be uploading new videos every Wednesday, so please subscribe to our channel!
This time we have with us Yoshiharu Yamazaki of Beyonz Ame no Mori Kawahama and Miyo Hirai of Beyonz Seasonings.
Farewell.